AKSHITA AGARWAL

Phone: +91-8562814568

Email: akshitaagarwal17@gmail.com

Address: 4/177a, Malviya Nagar, Jaipur, 302017 (Raj.)

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Organised, collaborative, and highly skilled React Native & iOS developer with 4.7+ years of professional experience in dynamic and deadline-driven environment. Ready to work closely with both teams customer to identify most efficient and beneficial solutions for process improvement.

SKILLS

MVC, Payment gateways Integration	Experienced	3rd party SDKs and API's Integration	Expert
JavaScript-Node	Expert	Testing and maintenance	Experienced
Redux, Redux-Thunk, NPM, Axios	Expert	OOPs, Swift 5, React Native	Expert

GIT, CI-CD Skillful

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

March 2022 – Present Ahmedabad, Gujarat

React Native & iOS, Bacancy Technology Pvt Ltd.

- Created reusable components that can be applied to react native applications
- Maintain app quality by Unit Testing
- Worked under Agile planning, and completed expected deliverables on time for every sprint

Aug. 2019 –March 2022 Jaipur, Rajasthan

React Native & iOS, Punchh Tech India Pvt. Ltd.

- Worked with React Native Development Kit, to creating iOS and Android apps.
- Maintain app quality by Unit Testing
- Designed and developed base classes, framework classes and re-usable components.
- Implemented Google Map in React Native.
- Cooperating & communicating with other team members for efficient management works.

React Native & iOS, Dotsquares Technologies Pvt. Ltd

Nov. 2017 – May. 2019 Jaipur, Rajasthan

- Good Understanding of Swift Basics.
- Implemented Redux in React Native.
- Technical knowledge of MVC application design.
- Implemented Google Map in React Native. And also familiar with JSON.

EDUCATION

Jul. 2020	MCA: Computer Science			
	• SS Jain Subodh PG College - jaipur, Rajasthan			
Jul. 2018	• 84% Approx.			
	BCA: Computer Science			
	• SS Jain Subodh PG College - Jaipur, Rajasthan			
	• 85%			
March 2015	12th : Commerce Maths			
	• 68%			
March 2013	10th			
	• 75.5%			

PROJECTS

Academy Sports And Outdoors

• It's for shop Academy Sports + Outdoors for sporting goods, hunting, fishing and camping equipment.

Wild wing cafe

- User can order the food through the application and earn points on ordering food.
- User can unlock the redeemable using that points and also get offers for special campaign.

Jack's

- User can order the food through the application and earn points on ordering food.
- User can unlock the redeemable using that points and also get offers for special campaign.

Gyu-Kaku

• The Gyu-Kaku App makes it easy to earn rewards for eating the food, Earn points for every purchase you make and redeem them for tasty rewards!

ContactBids App

• Contact Bids app is used for auction purpose. In this a user can auction his assets and send an invitation link to their contacts about the auction of the asset. And an interested person can bid on the asset or exchange product on behalf of asset.

InHouse APP

• InHouse app is basically build for in-house purpose. It contain all module like Gallery, BlogList, NewsList, Restaurant, Product List, Job List and so on.

GymFlex

- GymFlex app is used generating a pass for a gym and show all nearby gym list and on map view.
- A user can buy a pass by doing payment through Apple Pay and Android Pay and Stripe on Backend.

Fitness App

• Fitness App is used for pregnant women. Fitness App provides exercise video according to the trimester. For video access, user needs to purchase the package for watch the video.

LINKS



https://www.linkedin.com/in/akshita-agarwal-8b629a12a/